Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Edgerton, John Warren (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - Edgren (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - Edlin, Harry D. (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - Edmund, W. (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - Edwards, Alfred Lewis (Box 21, Folder 754)
  - Edwards, Charles Atwood (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - Edwards, General C. R. (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - Edwards, Ernest A. (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - Edwards, Franklin (Box 21, Folder 756)
  - Edwards, Jonathan (Box 21, Folder 757-61)
  - Edwards, Jonathan, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - Edwards, Justin (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - Edwards, Richard Henry (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - Eells, William Woodward (Box 21, Folder 763)
  - Eggers, Melvin A. (Box 21, Folder 763)
  - Egleston, William Couch (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - Eglin, Benjamin (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - Ehrich, Lewis R. (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - Ehrich, Manfred W. (Box 21, Folder 765)
  - Ehrman, Benjamin F. (Box 21, Folder 765)
  - Eichelberger, Martin Smyser (Box 21, Folder 766)
  - Eicholtz, Leonard Henry (Box 21, Folder 766)
  - Eisenhower, Pres. Dwight David (Box 21, Folder 767-69)
  - Eisenman, Carl [Mrs. Victor F. Eisenman] (Box 21, Folder 770)
  - Elder, Samuel James (Box 21, Folder 771)
  - Elderkin, John (Box 21, Folder 771)
  - Eldridge, J. M. (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - Eliason, Eldridge Lyon (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - Eliot, Charles William (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - Eliot, Douglas Fitch Gilbert (Box 21, Folder 773)
  - Eliot, Ellsworth (Box 21, Folder 773)
  - Eliot, Jared (Box 21, Folder 774)
  - Elkin, William L. (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - Elliot, George F. (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - Elliott, Alonzo (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - Elliott, Carl F. (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - Elliott, Edward T. (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - Elliott, Stephen (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - Ellis, Joseph Roy (Box 21, Folder 777)
  - Ellis, Matt L. (Box 21, Folder 777)
  - Ellsworth, Duncan Stewart (Box 21, Folder 777)
  - Ellsworth, Henry L. (Box 21, Folder 778)
  - Ellsworth, Oliver (Box 22, Folder 779-80)
  - Ellwanger, William DeLancey (Box 22, Folder 781)
  - Ely, Arthur Howard (Box 22, Folder 781)
  - Ely, Charles W. (Box 22, Folder 781)
  - Ely, Edward Stiles (Box 22, Folder 782)
  - Ely, Ezra Stiles (Box 22, Folder 783)
  - Ely, Jay M. (Box 22, Folder 784)
  - Ely, Morris Upham (Box 22, Folder 784)
  - Ely, William (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Embree, William Dean (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Emerson, Thomas A. (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Emerson, Thomas Irwin (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Emerson, William B. (Box 22, Folder 786)
  - Emery, Cyrus (Box 22, Folder 786)
  - Emery, Lucilius A. (Box 22, Folder 786)
  - Emmett, Herman L. (Box 22, Folder 787)
  - Emmons, Horatio Nelson (Box 22, Folder 787)
  - Emmons, Julius (Box 22, Folder 788)
  - Emmons, Nathanael (Box 22, Folder 789)
  - Enders, Ostrom (Box 22, Folder 789)
  - Engel, Edward (Box 22, Folder 789)
  - Engle, Clyde (Box 22, Folder 790)
  - English, James Edward (Box 22, Folder 790)
  - Engs, George (Box 22, Folder 790)
  - Engstrom, H. G. (Box 22, Folder 791)
  - Ensminger, Ross E. (Box 22, Folder 791)
  - Epstein, Alvin (Box 22, Folder 791)
  - Ermentrout, Fritz Daniel (Box 22, Folder 792)
  - Escarra, Jean (Box 22, Folder 792)
  - Espy, Wallace S. (Box 22, Folder 792)
  - Este, William (Box 22, Folder 793)
  - Estes, Wyatt Collier (Box 22, Folder 794)
  - Estill, Joe Garner (Box 22, Folder 794)
  - Esty, Albert Henry (Box 22, Folder 795)
  - Ethier, Stephen M. (Box 22, Folder 795)
  - Eustis, William Tappan (Box 22, Folder 795)
  - Evans, Albert Jeffreys (Box 22, Folder 796)
  - Evans, Daniel A. (Box 22, Folder 796)
  - Evans, John Lewis (Box 22, Folder 796)
  - Evans, Kenneth R. (Box 22, Folder 797)
  - Evans, Lemuel R. (Box 22, Folder 797)
  - Evans, Philip S. (Box 22, Folder 797)
  - Evans, R., Jr. (Box 22, Folder 798)
  - Evans, William Weston (Box 22, Folder 798)
  - Evarts, Allen W. (Box 22, Folder 799)
  - Evarts, Maxwell (Box 22, Folder 800)
  - Evarts, William Maxwell (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - Everest, C. S. (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - Everett, T. W. [?] (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - Ewart, Charles Diven (Box 22, Folder 802)
  - Ewing, Auguste Berthold, Jr. (Box 22, Folder 802)
  - Ewing, Jack S. (Box 22, Folder 803)
  - Ewing, Martin Baum (Box 22, Folder 803)
  - Ewing, Nathaniel W. (Box 22, Folder 804)
  - Exton (Box 22, Folder 805)
  - Eyres, Thomas (Box 22, Folder 805)
  - Faber, Curt (Box 22, Folder 806)
  - Failing, V. R. G. (Box 22, Folder 806)
  - Fairbanks, Edward Taylor (Box 22, Folder 806)
  - Fairchild, Fred Rogers (Box 22, Folder 807)
  - Fairchild, Hal (Box 22, Folder 807)
  - Fairchild, Henry P. (Box 22, Folder 808)
  - Farley, H. Allen (Box 22, Folder 808)
  - Farlus, Ernest E. (Box 22, Folder 808)
  - Farmer, Malcolm (Box 22, Folder 809)
  - Farnam, Charles Henry (Box 22, Folder 809)
  - Farnam, Henry (Box 22, Folder 809)
  - Farnam, Henry Walcott (Box 22, Folder 810)
  - Farnam, William W. (Box 22, Folder 811)
  - Farnsworth, Paul Beecher (Box 22, Folder 812)
  - Farnsworth, Sidney Wilbur (Box 22, Folder 813)
  - Farnum, Henry W. (Box 22, Folder 814)
  - Farr, Charles Everett (Box 22, Folder 814)
  - Farr, Hollon Augustine (Box 22, Folder 815-19)
  - Farrar, John Chipman (Box 22, Folder 820)
  - Farrar, John X. (Box 22, Folder 820)
  - Farrington, Edward Sherman (Box 22, Folder 820)
  - Farrington, F. Allen (Box 22, Folder 821)
  - Farwell, Arthur Lincoln (Box 22, Folder 821)
  - Farwell, John Arthur, Jr. (Box 22, Folder 822)
  - Faulkner, James D. (Box 22, Folder 822)
  - Faxon, William Cleveland (Box 22, Folder 822)
  - Fay, G. O. (Box 22, Folder 823)
  - Fei, Hsing jen (Box 22, Folder 823)
  - Feiser, Jacob Plummer (Box 22, Folder 823)
  - Fellowes, Frank W. (Box 22, Folder 824)
  - Felton, J. B. (Box 22, Folder 824)
  - Fenn, Henry Anderson (Box 22, Folder 824)
  - Fenn, William Henry (Box 22, Folder 824)
  - Fennelly, Edward Galligan (Box 22, Folder 825)
  - Fergusson, Harvey (Box 22, Folder 825)
  - Fernow, Bernard Edward (Box 22, Folder 825)
  - Ferrell, Joseph L. (Box 22, Folder 826)
  - Ferris, H. B. (Box 22, Folder 826)
  - Ferris, William H. (Box 22, Folder 827)
  - Ferry, Charles Addison (Box 22, Folder 827)
  - Ferry, William Henry (Box 22, Folder 828)
  - Fewsmith, William (Box 22, Folder 828)
  - Ficks, Gerald (Box 23, Folder 829)
  - Field, David Dudley (Box 23, Folder 829)
  - Field, Henry M. (Box 23, Folder 830)
  - Field, John H. (Box 23, Folder 830)
  - Field, K. H. (Box 23, Folder 831)
  - Fields, Harry Alexander (Box 23, Folder 831)
  - Finch, Edward Ridley (Box 23, Folder 832)
  - Finch, Francis Miles (Box 23, Folder 832)
  - Fischer, Richard T. (Box 23, Folder 832)
  - Fisher, Alexander (Box 23, Folder 833)
  - Fisher, George Park (Box 23, Folder 834)
  - Fisher, George William (Box 23, Folder 834)
  - Fisher, Harold A. (Box 23, Folder 835-36)
  - Fisher, Irving (Box 23, Folder 837-38)
  - Fisher, James (Box 23, Folder 839)
  - Fisher, Samuel H. (Box 23, Folder 839)
  - Fisher, Samuel Ware (Box 23, Folder 839)
  - Fisk, John S. (Box 23, Folder 840)
  - Fitch, Charles Howard (Box 23, Folder 841)
  - Fitch, Eleazar Thompson (and wife) (Box 23, Folder 842-43)
  - Fitch, John B. (Box 23, Folder 844)
  - Fitch, Thomas (Box 23, Folder 845)
  - Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 23, Folder 845)
  - Fitzhugh, Robert Hughes (Box 23, Folder 846)
  - Fitzpatrick, John Bambridge (Box 23, Folder 847)
  - Fitzwater, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 847)
  - Flagg, Willard Cutting (Box 23, Folder 848)
  - Flagg, William F. (Box 23, Folder 849)
  - Flanders, James Greeley (Box 23, Folder 849)
  - Fleishman, Joel (Box 23, Folder 850-51)
  - Fleming, Robert Brown (Box 23, Folder 852)
  - Fletcher, J. S. (Box 23, Folder 852)
  - Flint, Joseph M. (Box 23, Folder 853)
  - Flint, Peter (Box 23, Folder 854)
  - Flow, Charles Bernard (Box 23, Folder 854)
  - Flynt, William N. (Box 23, Folder 854)
  - Foch, Marshal Ferdinand (Box 23, Folder 855)
  - Focillon, Henri (Box 23, Folder 855)
  - Foley, James (Box 23, Folder 856)
  - Follis, Richard Holden, Jr. (Box 23, Folder 856)
  - Fontanillas, Juan Manuel Salvado (Box 23, Folder 857)
  - Foord, William M. (Box 23, Folder 857)
  - Foote, Arthur E. (Box 23, Folder 858)
  - Foote, Charles J. (Box 23, Folder 858)
  - Foote, Henry Ward (Box 23, Folder 859)
  - Foote, Thaddeus (Box 23, Folder 859)
  - Forbes, Edwin Horace (Box 23, Folder 860)
  - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 23, Folder 861)
  - Ford, Seabury (Box 23, Folder 862)
  - Forman, Charles W. (Box 23, Folder 862)
  - Forrest, George Chandler (Box 23, Folder 862)
  - Forrest, Richard Earp (Box 23, Folder 862)
  - Foster, Allen E. (Box 23, Folder 863)
  - Foster, Charles H. (Box 23, Folder 863)
  - Foster, Eleazar K. (Box 23, Folder 863)
  - Foster, George (Box 23, Folder 864)
  - Foster, Harold D. (Box 23, Folder 864)
  - Foster, John (Box 23, Folder 864)
  - Foster, John Pierrepont Codrington (Box 23, Folder 864)
  - Foules, Charles Dougharty (Box 23, Folder 865)
  - Fowler, B. F. (Box 23, Folder 865)
  - Fowler, Charles Newell (Box 23, Folder 866)
  - Fowler, George Starkweather (Box 23, Folder 866)
  - Fowler, Horace W. (Box 23, Folder 867)
  - Fowler, R. H. (Box 23, Folder 867)
  - Fowler, Thomas Coolidge (Box 23, Folder 867)
  - Fowler, William (Box 23, Folder 868)
  - Fox, L. (Box 23, Folder 868)
  - Francis, Cyrus W. (Box 23, Folder 868)
  - Francis, Pomeroy T. (Box 24, Folder 869)
  - Franciscus, James Grover (Box 24, Folder 869)
  - Frank, George Snapel (Box 24, Folder 869)
  - Frank, Jerome (Box 24, Folder 870)
  - Frank, Waldo David (Box 24, Folder 871)
  - Franke, Albert (Box 24, Folder 872)
  - Franklin, Benjamin (Box 24, Folder 872)
  - Franklin, George Mayer (Box 24, Folder 873)
  - Franklin, George Seagrave (Box 24, Folder 873)
  - Franklin, William Hammond (Box 24, Folder 874)
  - Frear, Walter (Box 24, Folder 875)
  - Frede, Richard Spooner (Box 24, Folder 876)
  - Fredericks, John Jay (Box 24, Folder 876)
  - Freeborn, DeLancy (Box 24, Folder 876)
  - Freelander, Ronald (Box 24, Folder 877)
  - Freeman, Edgar W. (Box 24, Folder 877)
  - Freeman, Harrison Belknap (Box 24, Folder 878)
  - Freeman, Richard (Box 24, Folder 879)
  - Frelinghuysen, Peter H. B. (Box 24, Folder 879)
  - French, Charles J. (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - French, John Herndon (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - French, Joseph S. (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - French, Robert (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - Freud, Anna (Box 24, Folder 881)
  - Freund, Bertram (Box 24, Folder 882)
  - Frew, William Nimick (Box 24, Folder 882)
  - Friedman, Milton R. (Box 24, Folder 883)
  - Friend, Kennedy Turner (Box 24, Folder 883)
  - Frisbee, Samuel Hanna (Box 24, Folder 884)
  - Frissell, Hollis Burke (Box 24, Folder 885)
  - Frissell, Lewis Varick (Box 24, Folder 886)
  - Frissell, Sidney Dodd (Box 24, Folder 886)
  - Frohman, Raymond W. (Box 24, Folder 887)
  - Frost, Donald Franklin (Box 24, Folder 887)
  - Frost, Milton (Box 24, Folder 887)
  - Frost, Simeon Taylor (Box 24, Folder 888)
  - Frower, J. O. (Box 24, Folder 888)
  - Fukuokai, Hidei (Box 24, Folder 889)
  - Fuller, Edward Thurston (Box 24, Folder 889)
  - Fuller, Melville W. (Box 24, Folder 890)
  - Fuller, Thomas H. (Box 24, Folder 890)
  - Fuller, William Henry (Box 24, Folder 891)
  - Fulton, Dr. John F. (Box 24, Folder 892)
  - Fulton, L. E. (Box 24, Folder 893)
  - Funk, Frank Hamilton (Box 24, Folder 893)
  - Furbish, Edward Brown (Box 24, Folder 894)
  - Furcolowe, Foster (Box 24, Folder 894)
  - Furniss, Edgar S. (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Furseth, Ola H. (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Furst, Michael (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Gabriel, Leon M. (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Gadsden, Christopher Edwards (Box 24, Folder 896)
  - Gadsden, James (Box 24, Folder 896)
  - Gaffney, Leo V. (Box 24, Folder 897)
  - Gage [Charles] Brownell (Box 24, Folder 897)
  - Gaines, Fred (Box 24, Folder 897)
  - Gale, Edward Chenery (Box 24, Folder 898)
  - Gale, LeRoy (Box 24, Folder 898)
  - Gale, Samuel Chester (Box 24, Folder 899)
  - Gallagher, John (Box 24, Folder 899)
  - Gallagher, J. R. (Box 24, Folder 899)
  - Galland, Richard Irving (Box 24, Folder 900)
  - Gallaudet, Thomas Hopkins (Box 24, Folder 901)
  - Gallaway, Robert M. (Box 24, Folder 902)
  - Galliher, Herbert Parrish (Box 24, Folder 903)
  - Galpin, Stephen Kellogg (Box 24, Folder 904)
  - Galvin, William James, Jr. (Box 24, Folder 904)
  - Gandy, William W. (Box 24, Folder 904)
  - Gannett, Henry (Box 24, Folder 905)
  - Ganter, Maxwell (Box 24, Folder 905)
  - Gardner, Cecil B. (Box 24, Folder 905)
  - Gardner, Leroy U. (Box 24, Folder 906)
  - Gardner, Robert H. (Box 24, Folder 906)
  - Garland, Albert S. (Box 24, Folder 907)
  - Garland, Charles Stedman (Box 24, Folder 907)
  - Garland, Laurence S. (Box 24, Folder 908)
  - Garneau, Henri Comstock (Box 24, Folder 908)
  - Garner, Wendell R. (Box 24, Folder 908)
  - Garratt, George A. (Box 24, Folder 909)
  - Garrepy, Bob (Box 24, Folder 909)
  - Garrison, R. T. (Box 24, Folder 910)
  - Garside, Charles (Box 24, Folder 910)
  - Garston, Dr. Louis (Box 24, Folder 910)
  - Garvan, Anthony (Box 25, Folder 911)
  - Garvan, Peter Dunne (Box 25, Folder 911)
  - Garver, John Anson (Box 25, Folder 912)
  - Gates, Allen H. (Box 25, Folder 912)
  - Gates, Edward Everett (Box 25, Folder 913)
  - Gates, Franklin H. (Box 25, Folder 913)
  - Gates Fairbanks, Artemus W. (Box 25, Folder 914)
  - Gaul, Edward Linus (Box 25, Folder 914)
  - Gavegan, Edward James (Box 25, Folder 914)
  - Gaylord, Franklin Augustus (Box 25, Folder 915)
  - Gaylord, John Flavel (Box 25, Folder 915)
  - Gaylord, Joseph F. (Box 25, Folder 916)
  - Gaylord, William Standish (Box 25, Folder 916)
  - Geer, Isaac Wheeler (Box 25, Folder 917)
  - Gerry, Elbridge (Box 25, Folder 917)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett (Box 25, Folder 918)
  - Gibbs, Frederic (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - Gibbs, George (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - Gibbs, Josiah W. (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - Gibson, Randall Lee (Box 25, Folder 920)
  - Gifford, Stanley E. (Box 25, Folder 920)
  - Gilbert, Benjamin Thorne (Box 25, Folder 921)
  - Gilbert, Morgan (Box 25, Folder 921)
  - Gilbert, Prentiss Bailey (Box 25, Folder 922)
  - Gilbert, William Thacher (Box 25, Folder 922)
  - Gilder, Richard (Box 25, Folder 923)
  - Gilder, Richard W. (Box 25, Folder 923)
  - Gilkey, Charles Whitney (Box 25, Folder 923)
  - Gill, Charles Clifford (Box 25, Folder 924)
  - Gill, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 924)
  - Gillespie, James Metcalf (Box 25, Folder 924)
  - Gillett, Charles W. (Box 25, Folder 925)
  - Gilman, Bradley (Box 25, Folder 925)
  - Gilman, Charles (Box 25, Folder 926)
  - Gilman, Daniel C. (Box 25, Folder 926)
  - Gilman, Edward Whiting (Box 25, Folder 926)
  - Gilmore, Grant (Box 25, Folder 927)
  - Gilmour, Andrew James (Box 25, Folder 927)
  - Gilson, John Leo (Box 25, Folder 928-29)
  - Gipson, Lawrence H. (Box 25, Folder 930)
  - Gitlitz, Morris (Box 25, Folder 930)
  - Givan, Walker Forrest (Box 25, Folder 931)
  - Glasgow, Edward B. (Box 25, Folder 932)
  - Glass, Edgar T. (Box 25, Folder 933)
  - Gleason, Fred E. (Box 25, Folder 933)
  - Gleason, John Blanchard (Box 25, Folder 934)
  - Gleason, Lafayette Blanchard (Box 25, Folder 934)
  - Gleason, William Henry (Box 25, Folder 935)
  - Glover, Charles Carroll (Box 25, Folder 936)
  - Glover, Philliam (Box 25, Folder 936)
  - Glover, S. (Box 25, Folder 936)
  - Glueckfield, I. Benjamin (Box 25, Folder 937)
  - Goddard, Delano A. (Box 25, Folder 938)
  - Goddard, J. C. (Box 25, Folder 938)
  - Godfrey, John (Box 25, Folder 939)
  - Godsey, Frank W., Jr. (Box 25, Folder 940)
  - Goebel, Arthur (Box 25, Folder 940)
  - Goebel, William Arthur (Box 25, Folder 940)
  - Goetchins, J. M. (Box 25, Folder 941)
  - Goethals, General George Washington (Box 25, Folder 941)
  - Goetzmann, William H. (Box 25, Folder 942)
  - Goin, Edward Harold (Box 25, Folder 942)
  - Goldey, Harry S. (Box 25, Folder 942)
  - Goldsby, Richard A. (Box 25, Folder 943)
  - Goldsmith, Timothy H. (Box 25, Folder 944)
  - Goldstein, Abraham (Box 25, Folder 944)
  - Goldstein, Paul J. (Box 25, Folder 944)
  - Gooch, Frank A. (Box 25, Folder 945)
  - Goodale, George Frank (Box 25, Folder 945)
  - Goodell, Thomas Dwight (Box 26, Folder 946)
  - Goodenough, Arthur (Box 26, Folder 946)
  - Goodenough, Giles Frederic (Box 26, Folder 947)
  - Goodhart, Arthur L. (Box 26, Folder 948)
  - Goodhue, Jonathan Elbridge (Box 26, Folder 948)
  - Goodlett, Nicholas Minor (Box 26, Folder 949)
  - Goodman, Charles Holmes (Box 26, Folder 949)
  - Goodman, Jacob (Box 26, Folder 949)
  - Goodnow, Charles N. (Box 26, Folder 950)
  - Goodrich, Annie (Box 26, Folder 951)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A. (Box 26, Folder 952-53)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey William (Box 26, Folder 954)
  - Goodrich, Edward (Box 26, Folder 954)
  - Goodrich, Frank (Box 26, Folder 954)
  - Goodwin, Gilberta D. (Box 26, Folder 955)
  - Goodwin, Sheldon (Box 26, Folder 955)
  - Goodwin, Willis Blake (Box 26, Folder 956)
  - Goodyear, A. G. (Box 26, Folder 956)
  - Goor, A. Y. (Box 26, Folder 956)
  - Gordon, Edward J. (Box 26, Folder 957)
  - Gordon, John C. (Box 26, Folder 957)
  - Gordon, Nathaniel (Box 26, Folder 957)
  - Gordon, William Washington (Box 26, Folder 958)
  - Gormly, Edwin C. (Box 26, Folder 958)
  - Gorner, H. L. (Box 26, Folder 958)
  - Gorton, Henry Haven (Box 26, Folder 959-60)
  - Gott, Joseph W. (1873) (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - Gottsberger, Benjamin Britton (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - Gould, Charles (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - Gould, Edward Young (Box 26, Folder 962)
  - Gould, Gerald Blenkiron (Box 26, Folder 962)
  - Gould, John H. (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - Gowen, Benjamin S. (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - Graham, Allan Brown (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - Graham, Joseph Andrew (Box 26, Folder 964)
  - Graham, Shirley (Box 26, Folder 964)
  - Grant, Edward D. (Box 26, Folder 965)
  - Grant, James Benton (Box 26, Folder 965)
  - Graves, Mrs. Clifford L. (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - Graves, George Dana (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - Graves, Henry (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - Graves, Henry Solon (Box 26, Folder 967)
  - Graves, James Taylor (Box 26, Folder 968)
  - Graves, Richard Stayner (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - Graves, ? (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - Graves,?? (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - Gray, Allan (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - Gray, Hannah Holborn (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - Gray, John P., Jr. (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - Graziani, Sante (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - Greaves, W. Hubert (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Greeley, Arthur, W. (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Greely, John Nesmith (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Greely, William B. (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Green, Edmund Frank (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Green, Edward (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Green, Leon William (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Green, S. S. (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Greene, Zaidee E. (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - Greenberg, David (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - Greene, David (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - Greene, David Bright (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - Greene, Gardiner (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - Greene, George Nelson (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - Greene, George Shaw, Jr. (Box 26, Folder 975)
  - Greene, Jeremiah Evarts (Box 26, Folder 975)
  - Greene, P. F. (Box 26, Folder 976)
  - Greene, R. Henry (Box 26, Folder 976)
  - Greene, Thomas M. (Box 26, Folder 977)
  - Greene, William Saunders (Box 26, Folder 977)
  - Greene, [?] (Box 26, Folder 978)
  - Greenfield, Jane (Box 26, Folder 978)
  - Greenleaf, William E. (Box 26, Folder 978)
  - Greenway, G. L. (Box 26, Folder 979)
  - Greenway, John Campbell (Box 26, Folder 980-81)
  - Greenwood, Charles T. (Box 26, Folder 982)
  - Greenwood, Moses M. (Box 26, Folder 982)
  - Gregory, George Newton (Box 26, Folder 982)
  - Gregory, Henry Whitmore (Box 27, Folder 983)
  - Gregory, James Elliot (Box 27, Folder 983)
  - Grey, Earl (Box 27, Folder 983)
  - Grieb, Henry N. (Box 27, Folder 984)
  - Grien, Edmund F. (Box 27, Folder 984)
  - Griffin, D. J. (Box 27, Folder 984)
  - Griffin, Edward Dorr (Box 27, Folder 985)
  - Griffin, George Herman (Box 27, Folder 986)
  - Griffis, Dr. Elliot (Box 27, Folder 986)
  - Griggs, M. (Box 27, Folder 987)
  - Griggs, Theodore Wright (Box 27, Folder 988)
  - Gring, Ambrose D. (Box 27, Folder 988)
  - Grinnell, Frank Lansing (Box 27, Folder 988)
  - Grinnell, George B. (Box 27, Folder 989)
  - Grinnell, Morton (Box 27, Folder 989)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 27, Folder 989)
    - Photos of election (Box 27, Folder 990-92)
    - Inauguaration (Box 27, Folder 993)
    - Inauguartion - informal portraits (Box 27, Folder 994-995)
    - 250th Convocation - photos & cartoon (Box 27, Folder 996)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 27, Folder 996)
    - Inauguration - informal shots with various people (Box 27, Folder 997-98)
    - Last class before becoming president (Box 27, Folder 999)
    - with President Pusey of Harvard (Box 27, Folder 1000)
    - at New York Board of Trade Gold Medal Award Salute to the Arts (Box 27, Folder 1001)
    - with President Eisenhower & others (Box 27, Folder 1002)
    - ROTC review (Box 27, Folder 1003)
    - at English Speaking Union World Conference with Prince Phillip (Box 27, Folder 1004)
    - Informal class lecture (Box 27, Folder 1005)
    - Returns to office after illness (Box 27, Folder 1006)
    - at Commencement with John F. Kennedy (Box 27, Folder 1007)
    - at summer home with Frank O.H. Williams (Box 27, Folder 1008)
    - with old & new college deans (Box 27, Folder 1009)
    - Dean Keller Portrait (Box 27, Folder 1010)
    - Formal & informal portraits (Box 28, Folder 1011-16)
    - Informal & group photos at various events (Box 28, Folder 1017-1021)
    - Family portraits (Box 28, Folder 1022-1023)
    - Photos & articles re: death and funeral (Box 28, Folder 1024-1025)
    - Related photos (Box 28, Folder 1026)
  - Griswold, Charles Augustus (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - Griswold, Henry J. (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - Griswold, John (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - Griswold, Mary (Mrs. A. Whitney) (Box 28, Folder 1028-33)
  - Griswold, William E. S. 1899 (Box 29, Folder 1034)
  - Griswold, William E. S., Jr. 1934 (Box 29, Folder 1035)
  - Groce, Marvin (Box 29, Folder 1035)
  - Gross, Clifford A. (Box 29, Folder 1035)
  - Gross, Henry McCormick (Box 29, Folder 1036)
  - Grout, Alfred (Box 29, Folder 1037)
  - Grove, Jacob Houtz (Box 29, Folder 1038)
  - Grubb, William Irwin (Box 29, Folder 1038)
  - Grube, Franklin (Box 29, Folder 1039)
  - Gruener, Gustav Frederick (Box 29, Folder 1039)
  - Guerin, Henry F. (Box 29, Folder 1039)
  - Guernser, James S. (Box 29, Folder 1040)
  - Guicharnaud, J. (Box 29, Folder 1040)
  - Guiterman, John Milton (Box 29, Folder 1040)
  - Gulick, Sidney Lewis (Box 29, Folder 1041)
  - Gulliver, Art (Box 29, Folder 1041)
  - Gulliver, Ashbel Green (Box 29, Folder 1041)
  - Gunckel, Lewis Winters (Box 29, Folder 1042)
  - Gunn, Alexander Hunter (Box 29, Folder 1043)
  - Gunn, George M. (Box 29, Folder 1043)
  - Gunther, Whitman (Box 29, Folder 1044)
  - Gurney, Ramsdell (Box 29, Folder 1044)
  - H. R. H. Gustavus Adolphus, Crown Prince of Sweden (Box 29, Folder 1045)
  - Guthrie, J. D. (Box 29, Folder 1045)
  - Guthrie, William Dameron (Box 29, Folder 1045)
  - Haas, John F. (Box 29, Folder 1046)
  - Haas, Mary R (Box 29, Folder 1047)
  - Haasis, Ferdinand (Box 29, Folder 1047)
  - Haber, David Dagobert (Box 29, Folder 1047)
  - Hackett, William Henry (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - Hadden, Briton (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - Haddock, Charles A. (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - Hadley, Arthur T. (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - Photos (Box 29, Folder 1049-1051)
  - Group photos (Box 29, Folder 1052)
  - Photos of grave in Grove St. Cemetary (Box 29, Folder 1053)
  - Related photos and articles (Box 29, Folder 1054)
  - Caricature & related letters (Box 29, Folder 1055)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining II (Box 29, Folder 1056)
  - Hadley, Hamilton (Box 29, Folder 1056)
  - Hadley, Helen Morris (Box 29, Folder 1057)
  - [Mrs. Arthur Twining Hadley] (Box 29, Folder 1057)